<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>web design on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</title>
    <link>https://simondev.win/tags/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web design on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://simondev.win/tags/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 24 - Power lays in cooperation</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/024/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a solution to a problem with my Mentor We connected through discord, the bot no longer reminds us of meetings because flexibility works better than top-down fixed days and times for meetings.
I introduced my mentor to my blog and told him how I created it. I also talked about the problems I encountered along the way and the ones I am currently facing.
Another domain problem needed to be fix When you typed in the name of my new domain simondev.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20 - Workflows, submodules and monorepo</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/020/</guid>
      <description>I A Git workflow is a recipe or recommendation for how to use Git to accomplish work in a consistent and productive manner.
Workflows are designed to be guidelines rather than concrete rules.
The Centralized Workflow uses a central repository to serve as the single point-of-entry for all changes to the project. This workflow doesn’t require any other branches besides &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo;.
The core idea behind The Feature Branch Workflow is that all feature development should take place in a dedicated branch instead of the main branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 18 - A bit of web-design knowledge</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/018/</guid>
      <description>How web developers deal with unexpected long texts in buttons[because of cms source of content]? They deal with it by adding some padding. (ProudEminem.png)
What pug is and what can provide for me in this task [don&amp;rsquo;t have to repeat changes in each file if I want to change something in the website layout] (https://github.com/pugjs/pug ) Pug is a kind of extension for HTML that makes our work easier.
We can see how it works in this site (Syntax part): https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 - Web design basics</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/004/</guid>
      <description>Difference between mobile first and desktop first design It&amp;rsquo;s all about priority.
You have the oportunnity to choose what&amp;rsquo;s more important for your clients / users of your website.
In desktop first design we focus on making good-looking website on desktop devices and then we think how to convert it or how to prepare that site for mobile screens.
In mobile first design, we do straight opposite. We start with building functional and pretty mobile website and then we think what to add, that we use whole desktop potential.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
