<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Organization on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</title>
    <link>https://simondev.win/categories/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organization on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://simondev.win/categories/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 22 - A summary of my learning</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/022/</guid>
      <description>Summary of previous months and some conclusions So I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed how big mistake I&amp;rsquo;ve done.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t make notes about anything I&amp;rsquo;ve done and learned during the last dozens of days.
I learned how to deploy a site (like this blog) using static site generator like Hugo. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how it works and how can I menega this kind of sites.
I&amp;rsquo;ve done some exercises that kept me in ,,programming&amp;quot; form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 - A Helpful Bot</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/003/</guid>
      <description>Making Discord Bot Today I had to create Bot for my Discord server. His responsibility should be reminding every member of channel #general about meeting.
It supposed to be done on Wednesday and Saturday morning and one hour before meeting which is at 8pm.
At first I took word ,,create&amp;quot; too serious and I started to learn how to make your own Bot and how to program it in JavaScript or Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 - Start of the journey</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/001/</guid>
      <description>First meeting with my new (and first) programming mentor Mateusz Grochowski.
Creating an honor agreement between the two of us about the work and responsibilities we will have in my programming journey.
Creating a channel on Discord and a planning to make a bot that reminds us about meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
