<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Website on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</title>
    <link>https://simondev.win/categories/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Website on Simon The Rising Front-End Star</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://simondev.win/categories/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 25 - CI/CD</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/025/</guid>
      <description>A week off I was absent for a week, due to my position in life. I am in the last year of high school and I am preparing for The Final Exam, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have much time nowadays. I&amp;rsquo;m explaining myself here only in front of&amp;hellip; myself! I feel bad when I can&amp;rsquo;t pay that much atention to study programming as I should, so I&amp;rsquo;m about to changing that. Work daily Simon, small steps - but daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24 - Power lays in cooperation</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/024/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a solution to a problem with my Mentor We connected through discord, the bot no longer reminds us of meetings because flexibility works better than top-down fixed days and times for meetings.
I introduced my mentor to my blog and told him how I created it. I also talked about the problems I encountered along the way and the ones I am currently facing.
Another domain problem needed to be fix When you typed in the name of my new domain simondev.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 23 - The Domain, changing DNS, experiements with site layouts</title>
      <link>https://simondev.win/posts/023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simondev.win/posts/023/</guid>
      <description>Purchase of a domain My blog is put up using Hugo&amp;rsquo;s static page generator and using Netlify, which hosts this site.
I had to buy a domain because the one from Netlify was a bunch of random words and numbers.
A mentor recommended porkbun.com to me and suggested .dev as a top-level domain. It would be suitable for me, as I want to become a web developer. However, it was a bit too expensive for me, since I live in Poland and dollars don&amp;rsquo;t convert with my currency very optimistically :D</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
